Guide to the Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 5 1870-2017
Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 5
- Mitre Corporation, Publication (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - Item 7: "Made Possible by a grant from Mobil" A Guide to Mobil's Support of Arts and Culture, Publication (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - Item 8: Facts about Mobil Corporation, Publication (Box 20, Folder 30)
    Full year, 1990. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Mobil World Vol. 57, No. 3: Special Issue, Publication (Box 20, Folder 30)
    March 1991. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Mobil at 125, Publication (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - Item 11: A Brief History of Mobil, Publication (Box 20, Folder 30)
- Mobil Oil Corporation - Handbooks, manuals, etc., Publication (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - Item 1: Chronological Fact Sheet, Publication (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - Item 2: Foreward: A publication for Montgomery Ward people, Publication (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - Item 3: Forecast of Potential, Publication (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - Item 4: Appraisal of Performance, Publication (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - Item 5: Correspondence Concerning Objective Setting and Appraisal Program Supplement, Publication (Box 20, Folder 31)
    January 14, 1980. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Correspondence Concerning Guidelines for the Objective Setting and Appraisal Program, Publication (Box 20, Folder 31)
    January 7, 1980. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Objectives/Action Plan Record Sheet, Publication (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - Item 8: Montgomery Ward & Co. The End of "Caveat Emptor", Publication (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - Item 9: Montgomery Ward: The End of "Caveat Emptor", Publication (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - Item 10: Montgomery Ward Facts: Chronological Fact Sheet, Publication (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - Item 11: Montgomery Ward News Service: Reaching New Goals, Publication (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - Item 12: Montgomery Ward: Leadership in Retailing, Publication (Box 20, Folder 31)
- Montgomery Ward & Company - Handbooks, manuals, etc., Publication (Box 20, Folder 32)
  - Item 1: Monsanto, Publication (Box 20, Folder 32)
  - Item 2: Your Future and Monsanto, Publication (Box 20, Folder 32)
  - Item 3: The New World of Monsanto, Publication (Box 20, Folder 32)
  - Item 4: Helping create the employe climatea contribution you can make a a Personnel Professional at Monsanto, Publication (Box 20, Folder 32)
  - Item 5: Your Future and Monsanto, Publication (Box 20, Folder 32)
- Monsanto - Handbooks, manuals, etc., Publication (Box 20, Folder 33)
  - Item 1: Products and Services: For Every Business Recordkeeping Requirement, Publication (Box 20, Folder 33)
  - Item 2: First Day Checklist--Administration, Publication (Box 20, Folder 33)
  - Item 3: Employee Progress Appraisal Form, Publication (Box 20, Folder 33)
  - Item 4: A Career with Moorethe Sky is the Limit, Publication (Box 20, Folder 33)
  - Item 5: Moore and YouA Bright Future Together!, Publication (Box 20, Folder 33)
- Moore Business Forms, Inc. - Handbooks, manuals, etc., Publication (Box 20, Folder 34)
  - Item 1: The Morgan Guaranty Survey, Publication (Box 20, Folder 34)
  - Item 2: The Morgan Guaranty Survey, Publication (Box 20, Folder 34)
  - Item 3: The Morgan Guaranty Survey, Publication (Box 20, Folder 34)
- Morgan Guaranty Trust Company, Publication (Box 20, Folder 35)
  - Item 1: Morton F. Plant Hospital Program, Publication (Box 20, Folder 35)
- Morton F. Plant Hospital, Publication (Box 20, Folder 36)
  - Item 1: Saving Energy! Motor Vehicle Manufacturers Meet the Challenge with New ProductsNew Systems, Publication (Box 20, Folder 36)
  - Item 2: Consumer Advisory: Methaol-Gasoline Blends Can Cause Serious Problems to Motor Vehivles, Publication (Box 20, Folder 36)
  - Item 3: MVMA, Publication (Box 20, Folder 36)
  - Item 4: Career Opportunities in Automotive Service, Publication (Box 20, Folder 36)
  - Item 5: Robotic Safety Conference, Publication (Box 20, Folder 36)
    June 1-2, 1983. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: A New Dawn for the Transportation Industry, Publication (Box 20, Folder 36)
    April 8, 1980. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: "Introduction to MORT Techniques" A Workshop on Systems Safety, Publication (Box 20, Folder 36)
    March 26-27 or March 28-29, 1984. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Your Way to Better Fuel Economy, Publication (Box 20, Folder 36)
    June, 1981. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Directory of Motor Vehicle Related Associations, 1981 Edition, Publication (Box 20, Folder 36)
  - Item 10: Motor Vehicles Manufacturers Association: What it is, What it Does, Publication (Box 20, Folder 36)
  - Item 11: Sound & Noise, Publication (Box 20, Folder 36)
  - Item 12: America Runs on Wheels: The National Scope of the Motor Vehicle Industry, Publication (Box 20, Folder 36)
  - Item 13: MVMA News Release for Immediate Release, Publication (Box 20, Folder 36)
  - Item 14: How to Save Truck Fuel, Publication (Box 20, Folder 36)
    October, 1982 Edition. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: The Truck & Bus Manufacturing Industry: Building the Tools That Move America, Publication (Box 20, Folder 36)
  - Item 16: Heavy Truck Safetythe Need to Know, Publication (Box 20, Folder 36)
  - Item 17: Remarks by V. J. Adduci, Publication (Box 20, Folder 36)
    By V. J. Adduci. October 26, 1983. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: Remarks by V. J. Adduci, Publication (Box 20, Folder 36)
    By V. J. Adduci. October 20-22, 1983. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: Remarks by Thomas F. Longerbeam, Publication (Box 20, Folder 36)
    By Thomas F. Longerbeam. October 13, 1983. Item is in English.
  - Item 20: Remarks by V. J. Adduci, Annual Meeting, Publication (Box 20, Folder 36)
    By V. J. Adduci. October 3, 1983. Item is in English.
  - Item 21: Remarks by Lawrence E. Slimak, 32nd Annual Conference, Publication (Box 20, Folder 36)
    By Lawrence E. Slimak. September 27, 1983. Item is in English.
  - Item 22: Dr. Fred W. Bowditch before The Society of the Plastics Industry of Canada, Publication (Box 20, Folder 36)
    By Dr. Fred W. Bowditch. September 27, 1983. Item is in English.
  - Item 23: The Automobile Engine and Alternate Fuels, Publication (Box 20, Folder 36)
    By Harry B. Weaver. September 15, 1983. Item is in English.
  - Item 24: Statement of Motor Vehicle Manufacturers Association of the United States, Inc., Publication (Box 20, Folder 36)
    By Dr. Fred W. Bowditch. November, 1983. Item is in English.
  - Item 25: Remarks by Lawrence Slimak: The 1990 Vehicle, Publication (Box 20, Folder 36)
    By Lawrence Slimak. November 15, 1983. Item is in English.
  - Item 26: Remarks by V. J. Adduci, 24th Annual Convention: Hawaii Automobile Dealers Association, Publication (Box 20, Folder 36)
    By V. J. Adduci. November 18, 1983. Item is in English.
  - Item 27: Remarks by V. J. Adduci: National Hghway Safety Symposium, Publication (Box 20, Folder 36)
    By V. J. Adduci. February 28, 29 and March 1, 1984. Item is in English.
  - Item 28: MVMA News Release, Collection of News Releases, Publication (Box 20, Folder 36)
  - Item 29: MVMA News Release, Collection of News Releases, Publication (Box 20, Folder 36)
  - Item 30: Robotic Safety Presented at the National Safety Congress, Publication (Box 20, Folder 36)
    October 19, 1983. Item is in English.
  - Item 31: MVMA 1984 Motor Vehicle Information, Publication (Box 20, Folder 36)
- Motor Vehicle Manufacturers Association - Handbooks, manuals, etc., Publication (Box 20, Folder 37)
- Mt. Sinai Occupational Medicine Clinic - We Care to Work, Not to Die: A Conference for People of Color and Low Wage Workers on How to Improve Safety and Health at Our Workplaces, February 23, 1991, Publication (Box 21, Folder 1)
- Nabisco Inc. "Employee Benefits", 1982; Publication (Box 21, Folder 2)
- Nabisco - Handbooks, manuals, etc., Publication (Box 21, Folder 3)
- National Academy of Arbitrators - Handbooks, Manuals, etc., Publication (Box 21, Folder 4)
- National Academy of Management Development, Publication (Box 21, Folder 5)
- National Alliance of Business, Publication (Box 21, Folder 6)
- NAACP, Publication (Box 21, Folder 7)
- Nat'l. Assoc. of Aluminum Distributors, Publication (Box 21, Folder 8)
- National Association of Employers on Health Care Alternatives, Publication (Box 21, Folder 9)
- Nat'l. Assoc. of Home Builders, Publication (Box 21, Folder 10)
- National Association of Manufacturers - Handbooks, manuals, etc., Publication (Box 21, Folder 11)
- National Association of Plastic Fabricators, Publication (Box 21, Folder 12)
- National Association of Printers and Lithographers, Publication (Box 21, Folder 13)
- National Association of Printers & Lithographers, Publication (Box 21, Folder 14)
- Nat'l. Assoc. of Securities Dealers, Publication (Box 21, Folder 15)
- National Assoc. of Suggestion Systems - House Organs, Publication (Box 21, Folder 16)
- National Association of Suggestion Systems, Publication (Box 21, Folder 17)
- National Assoc. of Temp Services, Publication (Box 21, Folder 18)
- National Association of Working Women, Publication (Box 21, Folder 19)
- National Cash Register, Publication (Box 21, Folder 20)
- National Cash Register, Publication (Box 21, Folder 21)
- National Coal Association, Publication (Box 21, Folder 22)
- National Commission on Working Women, Publication (Box 21, Folder 23)
- National Commission on Working Women and Women's Work Force Network of Wider Opportunities for Women, Publication (Box 21, Folder 24)
- National Committee for Full Employment, Publication (Box 21, Folder 25)
- National Committee on Pay Equity, Publication (Box 21, Folder 26)
- National Committee on Pay Equity, Publication (Box 21, Folder 27)
- National Conference on Religion & Labor, Publication (Box 21, Folder 28)
- National Coordinating Committee for Multi-Employer Plans, Publication (Box 21, Folder 29)
- National Coordinating Committee for Multiemployer Plans, Publication (Box 21, Folder 30)
- National Council on Alcoholism, Publication (Box 21, Folder 31)
- Nat'l. Council on Compensation Insurance, Publication (Box 21, Folder 32)
- National Council on Employment Policy, Publication (Box 21, Folder 33)
- National Council of Jewish Women, Publication (Box 21, Folder 34)
- National Electrical Manufacturers Assoc. - Handbooks, manuals, etc., Publication (Box 21, Folder 35)
- National Erectors Association, Publication (Box 21, Folder 36)
- National Export Traffic League, Publication (Box 21, Folder 37)
- National Farmers Union - Handbooks, manuals, etc., Publication (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Data on the National Farmers Union of the USA, Publication (Box 22, Folder 1)
    By National Farmers Union. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Farmers Union: Questions and Answers, Publication (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Know Your Farmer's Union, Publication (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: Farmers Union, Publication (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: Welcomes a New Member: 70 Years of Service to Agriculture, Publication (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: Farmers Union Policy Leaflet No. 11 For this we stand, Publication (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Item 7: The Voice of the Family Farmer: A Short History of the Farmers Educational and Cooperative Union of America, Publication (Box 22, Folder 1)
    By C.E. Huff and Perry Eberhart. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Highlights of Agricultural Progress: Farmers Union 70 Years of Service to Farmers, Publication (Box 22, Folder 1)
    By Milton D. Hakel. Item is in English.
- National Federation of Independent Business, Publication (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Small-Businesses Will Choose Layoffs, Shutdowns If Forced to Offer Health Benefits, Survey Shows, Publication (Box 22, Folder 2)
    By National Federation of Independent Business. July 19, 1989. Item is in English.
- National Foremen's Institute, Inc., Publication (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Superviding the Woman War Worker, Publication (Box 22, Folder 3)
    By National Foremen's Institute, Inc. Item is in English.
- Nat'l. Industrial Distributors Assoc., Publication (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Profile of an Industrial Distributor, Publication (Box 22, Folder 4)
    By National Industrial Distributors Association. Item is in English.
- National Institute for Labor Relations Research, Publication (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Journal of Labor Research Vol. XII No. 1, Publication (Box 22, Folder 5)
    By National Institute for Labor Relations Research. Winter 1991. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Letter to Librarian from Sybil B. Jones, Program Director, Publication (Box 22, Folder 5)
    By National Institute for Labor Relations Research. May 21, 1991. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: A Higher Standard of Living in Right to Work States, Publication (Box 22, Folder 5)
    By James T. Bennett. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: A Higher Standard of Living in Right-to-Work States, Publication (Box 22, Folder 5)
    By James T. Bennett, Ph.D. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Right to Work States Have Higher Real Income, New Study Shows, Publication (Box 22, Folder 5)
    By National Institute for Labor Relations Research. April 28, 1995. Item is in English.
- National Institute for Work and Learning and Coalition of Labor Union Women, Publication (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Groww: Project Opportunity, Publication (Box 22, Folder 6)
    By National Institute for Work and Learning and Coalition of Labor Union Women. Item is in English.
- Nat'l. Insulation Contractors Assoc., Publication (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Order Today!: Safety Materials, Publication (Box 22, Folder 7)
    By National Insulation Contractors Association. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The Insulation Industry's Disputes Settlement Plan, Publication (Box 22, Folder 7)
- National Kitchen Cabinet Association, Publication (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: NKCA's Comprehensive Guide to Services for Kitchen Cabinet Manufactureers & Their Suppliers, Publication (Box 22, Folder 8)
    By National Kitchen Cabinet Association. July 1980. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Directory of Sales Aids and Audio-Visuals for Certified Cabinets, Publication (Box 22, Folder 8)
    By National Kitchen Cabinet Association. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Directory of NKCA Certified Cabinets, Publication (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Item 4: NKCA Antitrust Guide, Publication (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Item 5: Recommended Construction & Performance Standards for Kitchen and Vanity Cabinets, Publication (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Item 6: NKCA: 1981 Income & Expense Study, Publication (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Item 7: 1981 Income & Expense Study Growth Indicator 50 A. Sales % of Prior Year- Constant $, Publication (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Item 8: Wage and Labor Information Study Edition of 1980, Publication (Box 22, Folder 8)
- National Labor Committee in Support of Worker and Human Rights, Publication (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Letter to Friends from Charlier Kernaghan, Publication (Box 22, Folder 9)
    By National Labor Committee in Support of Worker and Human Rights. Ocotber 1, 1998. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Letter to Friends of the NLC, Publication (Box 22, Folder 9)
    By National Labor Committee in Support of Worker and Human Rights. April 2001. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: "Made in the USA"?: Nightmare at the Daewoosa factory in America Samoa: A Report by the National Labor Committee, Publication (Box 22, Folder 9)
    By National Labor Committee in Support of Worker and Human Rights. March 2001. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: The People's Right to Know Campaign: A Call for Corporate Disclosure, Publication (Box 22, Folder 9)
    By National Labor Committee in Support of Worker and Human Rights. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Nightmare at the Daewoosa Factory in American Samoa, Publication (Box 22, Folder 9)
- National Labor Committee in Support of Worker & Human Rights in Central America, Publication (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: The US in Haiti: How to get rich on 11 cents an hour: A Report for the National Labor Committee Education Fund in Support of Worker and Human Rights in Cental America, Publication (Box 22, Folder 10)
    By National Labor Committee in Support of Water & Human Rights in Central America. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Paying to Lose Our Jobs, Publication (Box 22, Folder 10)
- National Labor Committee in Support of Democracy and Human Rights in El Salvador - Worker Rights and the New World Order: El Salvador, Guatemala June 1991, Publication (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Worker Rights and the New World Order: El Salvador, Honduras, Guatemala, Publication (Box 22, Folder 11)
    By National Labor Committee in Support of Democracy and Human Rights in El Salvador. June 1991. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Worker Rights and the New World Order: El Salvador, Honduras, Guatemala, Publication (Box 22, Folder 11)
    By National Labor Committee in Support of Democracy and Human Rights in El Salvador. Junw 1991. Item is in English.
- National Leadership Coalition on AIDS, Publication (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Business and Labor speak out on AIDS, Publication (Box 22, Folder 12)
    By National Leadership Coalition on AIDS. Item is in English.
- National Legal & Policy Center, Publication (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Teamsters Money-Laundering Schemes, Publication (Box 22, Folder 13)
    By National Legal & Policy Center. Item is in English.
- National Management Association - Handbooks, manuals, etc., Publication (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Your Guide to Service: Services, Courses and Programs, Publication (Box 22, Folder 14)
    By National Management Association. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: What's in a management club for you?, Publication (Box 22, Folder 14)
    By Anthony Mastey. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: NMA Can't tell you where you're going, but it can help you get there, Publication (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Item 4: Management as a Career, Publication (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Item 5: Manage Second Quarter 1986 "American Manager of the Year", Publication (Box 22, Folder 14)
- National Manpower Institute - Handbooks, manuals, etc., Publication (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Report, Publication (Box 22, Folder 15)
    By National Manpower Institute. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Report, Publication (Box 22, Folder 15)
- National Older Workers Information System, Publication (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Nowis Ideapac: Personnel Practices for an Aging Work Force, Publication (Box 22, Folder 16)
    By National Older Workers Information System. Item is in English.
- National Organization for Women, Publication (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Lets Stand Together: The Story of Ella MaeWiggings, Publication (Box 22, Folder 17)
    By National Organization for Women. September 14, 1979. Item is in English.
- National Railroad Adjustment Board, Publication (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Construction of Contracts: Principles of Interpretation of Agreements, Publication (Box 22, Folder 18)
    By National Railroad Adjustment Board. Item is in English.
- National Resource Center for Consumers of Legal Services, Publication (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Men's Clothing Industry, Publication (Box 22, Folder 19)
    By National Recovery Administration. August 26, 1933. Item is in English.
- National Restaurant Assoc. - Handbooks, manuals, etc., Publication (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Legal Services & the Labor Movement, Publication (Box 22, Folder 20)
    By National Resource Center for Consumers of Legal Services. Item is in English.
- National Right to Work Committee, Publication (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: A Glowing Year Ahead: Foodservice Sales to top $157 billion in 1984, Publication (Box 22, Folder 21)
    By National Restaurant Association. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The Foodservice Industry: 1981, Publication (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Item 3: Catalog of Publications, Publication (Box 22, Folder 21)
    By National Restaurant Association. 1987-1988. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Position Papers, Publication (Box 22, Folder 21)
    By National Restaurant Association. September 1990. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Catalog of Publications, Publication (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Item 6: Communication, Publication (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Item 7: Letter to Member Vol. 7 NO. 46, Publication (Box 22, Folder 21)
    By National Restaurant Association. November 16, 1987. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: The National Restaurant Association: Who We Are, Publication (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Item 9: New Member Dues, Publication (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Item 10: The National Restaurant Association presents: A Galaxy of Benefits for Every Foodservice Operator, Publication (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Item 11: Public Affairs Conference, Publication (Box 22, Folder 21)
- National Right to Work - Legal Defense Foundation, Publication (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Protestantism and the Right to Work, Publication (Box 22, Folder 22)
    By Dr. Frederick Curtis Fowler. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Political Realities vs. Moral Principle, Publication (Box 22, Folder 22)
    By Reed Larson. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: The Fight for 14(B): The Story of Senator Everett M. Dirksen's Battle to Preserve the Right to Work, Publication (Box 22, Folder 22)
    By National Right to Work Committee. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Public Attitudes Toward Right to Work Laws, Publication (Box 22, Folder 22)
    By National Right to Work Committee. March 1980. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Issue Briefing Paper, Publication (Box 22, Folder 22)
    By National Right to Work Committee. May 20, 1980. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Foundation News Review, Publication (Box 22, Folder 22)
    By National Right to Work Committee. April 14, 1982. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Right to Work: News Service, Publication (Box 22, Folder 22)
    By National Right to Work Committee. June 3, 1980. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Right to Work: News Service, Publication (Box 22, Folder 22)
    By National Right to Work Committee. June 29, 1984. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Letter to Editor, Publication (Box 22, Folder 22)
    By National Right to Work Committee. August 31, 1983. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Issue Briefing Paper, Publication (Box 22, Folder 22)
    By National Right to Work Committee. September 1987. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Issue Briefing Paper, Publication (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Item 12: Letter to Congressman, Publication (Box 22, Folder 22)
    By National Right to Work Committee. June 1, 1983. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Letter to Senator, Publication (Box 22, Folder 22)
    By National Right to Work Committee. March 14, 1983. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Letter to Senator, Publication (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Item 15: Letter to Friend about the future of the Right to Work program, Publication (Box 22, Folder 22)
    By National Right to Work Committee. June 30, 1982. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: Letter about Legislation, Publication (Box 22, Folder 22)
    By National Right to Work Committee. May 23, 1983. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: Letter to Senator, Publication (Box 22, Folder 22)
    By National Right to Work Committee. May 27, 1983. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: Letter to Editorabout the Enmons Case, Publication (Box 22, Folder 22)
    By National Right to Work Committee. August 17, 1982. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: Bunker Hill: A Classic Case of Compulsory Unionism, Publication (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Item 20: Right to Work through the Cartoonist's Eye, Publication (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Item 21: Letter to Editor, Publication (Box 22, Folder 22)
    By National Right to Work Committee. September 27, 1982. Item is in English.
  - Item 22: Repeat te Davis-Bacon Act: One Million Petitions to Congress, Publication (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Item 23: Petition to US Senator and US Congressman about Davis-Bacon Act, Publication (Box 22, Folder 22)